cariszone.com 2010-11-21

# cariszone.com | Privacy Policy

Cariszone.com Privacy Policy

This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If our information practices change, we will post an updated policy on our website. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears above. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this policy at any time.

  ****What Personal Information about Customers does Cariszone.com gather?

****Does Cariszone.com share the Information it receives?

****How Secure is the Customer personal Information?

****What is ''Phishing''?

****What about links to other Websites?

**What Personal Information About Customers Does Cariszone.com Gather?**

The information obtained from customers helps us personalize and constantly develop your shopping experience at Cariszone.com. Here are the types of information we gather.   

**1.     Information Provided to Cariszone.com by the Customer**

We receive and save any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way.You can choose not to provide certain information,but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving your online shopping experience, and communicating with our customers. Cariszone.com collects personal Information on the basis of creating an account and placing an order, as follows:

Create an Account with Cariszone.com  
  
Contact Phone Number  
Email Address  
Billing & Shipping Information as it appears on your credit card account such as:  
Name as it appears on Card  
  
Mailing/Billing Address  

Process purchases on Cariszone.com

[A] Credit Card Information required from the customer:

Type of card (for example Visa or MasterCard)  
---  
Card Number  
CVV2 or Cardholder Verification Value*  
Expiration Date on the card  
Name as it appears on the card  
Billing Address  

*What is a CVV2?  
The CVV2 or Cardholder Verification Value helps ensure that the physical card is in the cardholder’s possessions while shopping online, helping to prevent unauthorized or fraudulent use, increasing protection against credit card fraud. The CVV2 is a 3 or 4-digit value printed in the card or signature strip but not encoded on the magnetic stripe. Online merchants who request this value in their transactions are forbidden from storing the information once the individual transaction is authorized and completed.

[B] Personal Information required from the Customer to process the order  
  
Full Name  
Mailing address / Billing Address and Shipping Address as it appears on the Credit Card.  

**  
2.     Automatic Information Received**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Cariszone.com or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Cariszone.com on other Web sites.

*What are Cookies?  

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as, recommended for you, & storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Cariszone.com's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Cariszone.com products and services that require you to Sign in.   

**3.     **E-mail Communications with Cariszone.com**  
**

> In order to assist us make e-mails more valuable and appealing, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Cariszone.com if your computer supports such capabilities. **  
> **

> **4.    **  Other Information You Give Us ****
> 
> You provide most such information when you search, buy, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; place an order through Cariszone.com; provide information in Your Account or Your Profile; communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; compile Wish list; participate in Discussion Boards or other forums; and provide a rating or review. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; credit card information; personal description and financial information, including National Identification & Driver's permit numbers. 

> ** 5.    **Information from Other Sources****
> 
> Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.
> 
> ** 6.    **Information You Can Access****
> 
> Examples of information you can access easily at Cariszone.com include up-to-date information regarding recent orders; personally identifiable information (including name, e-mail, password, e-mail notification settings (including Alerts, Recommended for You, and newsletters); shopping lists; Merchant seller accounts; and Your Profile (including your product reviews, requests, and recommendations, personal profile).

********Does Cariszone.com Share the Information it Receives?****

Information about our customers is an integral part of our business, and we disclaim remittance of such to any unauthorized person. Cariszone.com share customer information only as described below:   
  **  
**

> ****Third-Party Service Providers:**** ****  
> 
> 
> We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.  ****  
> ****
> 
> ****Protection of Cariszone.com and Others:**** ****  
> 
> 
> We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Cariszone.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. ********  
> ****
> 
> **** With Your Consent:** **  
> 
> 
> Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. **  
>  **

********How Secure is the Customer Personal Information?****

  1. Because we are committed to protecting the security of your information, when information is received,  and during transmission of information, we warrant safety of information by using **Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software**, which encrypts information you input. The Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology is a vital part of the security features offered by Cariszone.com and aims to protect cardholder information from being seen on the open Internet during a purchase transaction. For example when you enter your personal information on our website’s log in page, and you enter submit, the SSL technology is used to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. Another example is when you are about to make a purchase online and you enter all the relevant details as it pertains to yourself and your credit card; to make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser. If you see an ‘unbroken key’ or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from "http" to "https." If for any reason you cannot access the secure server, or if you're not quite comfortable shopping online at any websites, please feel free to place your order with us by telephone at the number listed in the section entitled, "Contact Cariszone.com", below.

  2. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate Credit Card Processor at the Local Financial Institution (Bank) during order processing. 

  3. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer or even your personal computer.

************What is "Phishing"?  
****  

"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through email.  
  
****  
**  
  
**********What About Links to Other Websites?**  
  
**

**** For your convenience and information, our websites may contain links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our sites. ****  
**** **  
**  
**  
**
